Hello everyone!
In this tutorial, what I'm gonna do is
give you a really quick basic introduction to the PHP language
and I'm not gonna go over everything there is to know about the PHP language
but I feel that if you wanna learn how to code PHP
there are several components to PHP that you should be aware of.
So let's just go ahead and get started here,
it's not gonna take too long.
So first of all, what is PHP?
If someone walks up to you and asks:
"Hey what is PHP? What does it stand for?"
Well, you should be able to respond with:
"Well, PHP is a hypertext preprocessor!"
So they gonna pretty much think you're pretty smart
to know what you are talking about.